[{"id": 2555, "question": "Bernie was smart and wanted to be his own boss.When Bernie was 25 he took a wife. Bernie had saved some money and decided on a dry goods and grocery store combined. Marie had a knack for arranging the merchandise to appeal to customers and Bernie didn't mind the long hours. He was happy, and life was good.The business thrived until the great depression hit the entire country. No one had money to purchase pretty things or even food. In 1930, Marie had a heart attack and left Bernie alone. Following Marie's death, which Bernie felt was brought about from worrying about the store, He lost interest in everything. He had few customers and did not make them feel welcome, Bernie wandered about the store , dusting a bit and sweeping the floor. His inventory remained almost the same, as nothing muc...\n\nQ: How did Bernie's business begin to improve ?", "options": ["With the help of Julie's family", "By selling the cheap fresh produce and food", "By means of planting vegetables and fruits", "By providing customers with different services."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3075, "question": "In our daily life, many of us feel stressed more or less. Some like this pressure and work better because of it. Others are not comfortable with any stress at alls they soon become unhappy if they feel stressed. Sometimes stress can lead people to do things they wouldn't usually do, such as overeat, smoke, drink, or use drugs. Streas, however, is a very normal part of life. It is important to understand that stress doesn't come from an event itself, that is, from the things that are happening in our lives. It comes from the meaning we give to what has happened. For example, a crying baby may be stressful to one person, but it may not bother another person at all, a traffic jam may be stressful to one person while another person may be able to stay calm. We can experience stress any time we...\n\nQ: From the text, we can conclude that  _  .", "options": ["if someone has stress he will do something wrong unavoidably", "anyone can experience stress when he is out of control", "one will feel no stress at all if he gets enough physical exercise.", "one is sure to work better because of the stress."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2326, "question": "Starting college can be a difficult experience. You have to deal with new responsibilities, growing independence, a challenging course load, and of course, the social scene. When a roommate is thrown into the mix, it may feel like you're struggling with all that stuff while living in a small box with a stranger. But having a roommate doesn't need to be one more thing to worry about. When students go into their living situations with realistic expectations and a willingness to _ , things can work out just fine. When you first meet your roommate, chances are that you'll be on your best behavior. You want to get along since this is the person who's going to be sharing your living space for the next year. But try to think ahead to potential worst cases, too. For example, imagine it's 2 am and ...\n\nQ: What should you do if your roommate interrupts your preparing for the final examination?", "options": ["Show anger to him or her.", "Blame him or her.", "Talk with him or her.", "Praise him or her."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 624, "question": "British newspapers are among the oldest and most famous in the world. But recently big changes have seen these traditional publications try to fit the modern world. After 221 years, The Times has changed its size to become much smaller. In fact, the paper has cut its size in half from a broadsheet to tabloid . In prefix = st1 /Britainthe newspaper market is divided between the larger broadsheets and the smaller tabloids. These terms refer to the size of the papers' pages but there is also a clear difference in content. Broadsheets such as The Times, the Guardian and Daily Telegraph are serious papers. They cover a broad range of political, economic and international issues. Their stories are also reasonably long and use quite formal language. Tabloids have far more stories about less serio...\n\nQ: In which year was The Times born?", "options": ["1782", "1785", "1788", "1786"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1134, "question": "The slogan \"a dog is for life, not just for Christmas\" has been going strong for 27 years now. Dogs and cats have been popular Christmas gifts in the gifts in the UK and Europe for many years. But some people still haven't quite got the message. The slogan still holds good. Some 105,000 dogs were _ by local government last year because they had been abandoned, many of them shortly after the festival season. The main reason given by owners for handing their dogs over to the Dogs Trust is that the dogs need more attention than they can give; behavioral problems and moving home are also reasons given. But Eleanor Silk, the Trust's communications director, says, \"It's often four or five months after Christmas, in early summer, when owners find that the dog has got too big and too active, or it...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Dogs and Cats--the Most Popular Christmas Gifts.", "A pet is for Life, Not just for Christmas.", "How to Take Care of Your Pets over Christmas.", "Let's Help Those Abandoned Pets"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2644, "question": "What teaches you more about China: learning the language or making friends with Chinese people? Doing both would be perfect of course and maybe some people would say you cannot separate the two. I arrived in China in September 2010 and have been fortunate over the last year to teach English at a small university in Zhejiang province,about half an hour from Hangzhou.Despite starting with the best of aims to learn Chinese.in each term something seemed to prevent me.In the first term it was a bad cold and judging some public English speech contests,and then my father's death sent me home for a while. But if I miss Chinese lessons this year I will make friends with several of the Chinese teachers at the university who also teach English.It's been a wonderful thing to be welcomed into their liv...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["What teaches you most about China?", "How do you make friends in China?", "What do you do with the Chinese language?", "How do you appreciate the most in China?"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2467, "question": "We human beings haven't been good friends to animals. For thousands of years, we have been polluting the environment, making it hard for animals to live on the planet. We have been killing animals for their fur, feathers or meat, or simply because they are dangerous. As a result, many kinds of animals have disappeared forever. Hundreds more are on the endangered list today. Should we care about animals? Of course we should. If animals of a certain kind all disappear, they will never come back again. Animals are more than just resources of things we need. Every kind of animal has its place in the balance of nature. Destroying any kind of animal can lead to many problems. For example, when farmers killed large numbers of hawks, the corn and grain that the farmers stored were destroyed by rat...\n\nQ: The text calls on us to  _  .", "options": ["keep animals at home", "protect the environment", "protect the endangered animals", "know more about the balance of nature."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1659, "question": "Scientists are developing the next generation of robot-driven cars and predict they could be carrying humans around by the year 2030. The first wave of intelligent robot cars, capable of understanding and reacting to the world around them, will be tested this November in a competition run by the US Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency. Scientists are developing vehicles which will not only be driven by robots independently, but will be able to operate in a complicated city environment. \"In the past it was _ for a vehicle just to perceive the environment,\" said Sebastian Thrun, a professor at Stanford University. \"The new challenge will be to understand the environment. The robot must be able to recognize another car, to understand that it is moving and that it will interact with it as...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is NOT true about \"Junior\"?", "options": ["Some of its parts have been modified by engineers.", "It is controlled by a robot or a computer.", "It was invented by Sebastian Thrun.", "It is valuable."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 628, "question": "British newspapers are among the oldest and most famous in the world. But recently big changes have seen these traditional publications try to fit the modern world. After 221 years, The Times has changed its size to become much smaller. In fact, the paper has cut its size in half from a broadsheet to tabloid . In prefix = st1 /Britainthe newspaper market is divided between the larger broadsheets and the smaller tabloids. These terms refer to the size of the papers' pages but there is also a clear difference in content. Broadsheets such as The Times, the Guardian and Daily Telegraph are serious papers. They cover a broad range of political, economic and international issues. Their stories are also reasonably long and use quite formal language. Tabloids have far more stories about less serio...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true according to the given information?", "options": ["There are more tabloids than broadsheets in Britainat present.", "After the change, there will be no differences between The Sun and The Times.", "Although The Times has cut its size, it remains a serious paper.", "All the papers will tend to have the same style in the future."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 268, "question": "Should doctors ever lie to benefit their patient---to speed recovery or to cover the coming of death? In medicine as in law, government, and other lines of work, the requirements of honesty often seem dwarfed by greater needs: the need to protect from brutal news or to uphold a promise of secrecy; to advance the public interest. What should doctors say, for example, to a 46-year-old man coming in for a routine physical check up just before going on vacation with his family who, though he feels in perfect health, is found to have a form of cancer that will cause him to die within six months. Is it best to tell him the truth? If he asks, should the doctor reject that he is ill, or minimize the gravity of the illness? Should they at least hide the truth until after the family vacation? Doctor...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["Whether patients should be told the truth of their illness.", "Whether patients really want to know the truth of their condition.", "Whether different studies should be carried on.", "Whether doctors are honest with their patients."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2897, "question": "Taylors English Language Preparation 2011 www.taylorscollege.edu.au/telp If you need additional help to gain the high level of English language necessary for academic study, Taylors English Language Preparation (TELP) is the perfect solution. Throughout your TELP studies you will be an active language learner. You will be surrounded by opportunities to communicate in English, with friends, teachers, families and local people. You will gain English language skills which you will keep for life. l English: the language of Taylors College Strong English language skills are necessary for success in your chosen Taylors program. The TELP program, delivered in 12 week terms, is specifically designed to provide language training for academic study. Our teachers are fully trained English Language Te...\n\nQ: What information will probably be provided following TELP term dates?", "options": ["TELP fees", "TELP description", "TELP courses", "TELP term dates in 2012"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 174, "question": "A gentleman put an advertisement in a newspaper for a boy to work in his office. Out of the nearly fifty men who come to apply, the man selected one and dismissed the others. \"I should like to know,\" said a friend, \"the reason you preferred that boy, who brought not a single letter--not a recommendation ,\" \"You are wrong\" said the gentleman. He had a great man. He wiped his feet at the door and closed the door after him, indicating that he was careful. He gave his seat immediately to that old man, showing that he was kind and thoughtful. He took off his cap when he came in and answered my questions, showing that he was polite and gentlemanly. \" All the rest stepped over the book which I had purposely put on the floor.\" He picked it up and placed it on the table; and he waited quietly for h...\n\nQ: A gentleman put an advertisement in a newspaper  _", "options": ["in order to hire an office boy", "so as to dismiss the others", "in order to select one among the fifty applicants", "so as to select one and dismiss the others"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1063, "question": "In recent years many countries of the world have been faced with the problem of how to make their workers more productive. Some experts claim the answer is to make jobs more varied. But do more various jobs lead to greater productivity? There is evidence to suggest that while variety certainly makes the worker's life more enjoyable, it does not actually make him work harder. As far as increasing productivity is concerned, then variety is not an important factor. Other experts feel that giving the worker freedom to do his job in his own way is important, and there is no doubt that this is true. The problem is that this kind of freedom cannot easily be given in the modern factory with its complicated machinery which must be used in a fixed way. Thus while freedom of choice may be important, ...\n\nQ: The best title for this passage may be   _  .", "options": ["Problems of Modern Workers", "Making Jobs More Interesting", "Pushing Workers to Produce More", "How to Improve Labor Conditions"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2291, "question": "Recreational tree climbing is taking root in the ecotourism industry, and it's sending guys like Tim Kovar to far off reaches of the globe. Kovar, a tree-climbing instructor, recently returned to the U.S. from Brazil, where he spent time developing a tree-climbing operation thanks to the \"slow travel\" movement. Slow travel, is like the slow food movement, the practice of giving fast food in favor of homegrown cooking--the kind that takes hours to prepare and enjoy. Likewise, slow travel urges visitors to experience a place's natural surroundings and learn about the ecology in a way not afforded by extreme games. \"Tree climbing is a slow activity,\" says Kovar. \"It's not something you do quickly and then you're on to the next thing or event.\" There is no such thing as a quick climb, especial...\n\nQ: What do we know about tree climbing from the passage?", "options": ["People compete to see who can climb to the top first.", "It favors the experience of enjoying nature.", "It is a kind of extreme sport and needs a lot of effort.", "People view it as a challenge to climb the tallest tree in a forest."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3399, "question": "Women love shoes! They will sometimes go to look for the perfect pair of shoes to wear only once with the perfect outfit or the fashion of the day. Once worn, these fashionable designer shoes may spend weeks, months, or years in the closet without being worn again until another special occasion comes up. With that said, are expensive designer shoes really worth their cost? Historically, shoes were invented to free feet from sharp rocks, hot sands, and blisters. Shoes were made to be simple and functional, with tough leather soles and straps. As society became more sophisticated , the role of shoes changed; shoes were made to add status to the wearer. Shoe designers began to work on the production of fashion shoes for the wealthy; shoes meant more for show than for practical use or simplici...\n\nQ: In this passage, the author wants to  _  .", "options": ["explain why expensive designer shoes are worth the money", "talk about the necessity of owning comfortable shoes", "warn women of the danger of wearing designer shoes", "talk about the history and development of shoes"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2184, "question": "Linda and Lucy were best friends. They graduated from high school and went to the same college for further studies. After some days Linda found that her friend was behaving strangely. She would remain quiet, sleep too much and turn wild, very often. At first, Linda thought it was just because of the problems she had met in her studies. However, Lucy became even stranger over time. Finally, Linda couldn't take it any longer and asked Lucy about her strange behavior. Lucy broke into tears and said that she was going around with a boy, who was taking drugs and forcing her to take them, too. Linda was shocked by her story. She then advised her friend to leave the boy. She reminded Lucy of her dreams of becoming a successful doctor and encouraged her to set an example for others. She also remin...\n\nQ: The following are Lucy's strange behaviors EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["turning wild", "being quiet", "sleeping too much", "being friendly"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2811, "question": "A lot more people are about to get a chance to buy Google Glass. It's the Internet-connected eyewear that has become the hottest sale. Google will sell the \"Explorer\" version of Glass to any U.S. person who places an online order for the device beginning at 9am. PDT April 15. The product will cost $1,500. Google is saying how many sets of Glass will be available during the limited-time offer. This version of Glass, though, still isn't the perfect product that Google hopes to sell in stores later this year. For now, Google is still trying to recruit more people willing to serve as volunteers for its attempt to build a wearable device that features some of the same feature as a smart phone. \" Our Explorers are moms, bakers, surgeons, rockers, and each new Explorer has brought a new view that...\n\nQ: What problem may Google Glass bring to people?", "options": ["Its screen is too small for people to surf the Internet.", "It may cause traffic accidents if people use it while driving.", "Users must use their hands to take photos.", "It is difficult for many people to learn to use."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2021, "question": ". Passage 1 Every morning, when we wake up, we have 24 brand-new hours to live. What a gift! We have the capacity to live in a way that these 24 hours will bring peace, joy, and happiness to ourselves and to others. Peace is right here and now, in ourselves and in everything we do and see. The question is whether or not we are in touch with it. We don't have to travel far away to enjoy the blue sky. We don't have to leave our city or even our neighborhood to enjoy the eyes of a beautiful child. Even the air we breathe can be a source of joy. We can smile, breathe, walk, and eat our meals in a way that allows us to be in touch with the abundance of happiness that is available. We are very good at preparing how to live, but not very good at living. We know how to sacrifice ten years for a di...\n\nQ: The author of Passage 1 would most likely respond to the \"argument\" (line 1 Passage 2) with   _   .", "options": ["absolute neutrality", "partial acceptance", "complete agreement", "surprised disbelief"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2612, "question": "Matt grow the best vegetables in the village.He grows fruit too--big , sweet apples and oranges.And what else ? Well , the biggest and the prettiest flowers.Things grow in Matt' s garden all through the year.He cuts some flowers for his sitting room table ; and of course , he eats some fruit and vegetables.But he sells everything else in the market.Matt is not a poor man. He knows a few other gardens ; but he does not have any friends.You might ask , \" What is that ? Why doesn ' t he have friends ? \" I will tell you.People do not understand him.And they do not understand his garden, \" Why not ? \" you will ask.\" It' s a very good garden , isn' t it ? \" It is a wonderful garden.Matt plants things in spring , summer and autumn and winter .After that he does very little work.He sits in the gar...\n\nQ: Everything in Matt' s garden grows well because    _", "options": ["he has a good garden", "he is good at growing things and likes listening to the radio", "music helps his plants a lot", "he is very hardworking"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1336, "question": "Simona lives in Bucharest, Romania. She is nine years old and HIV positive . When Simona's mother found out about her illness five years ago, her first reaction was to tell everyone, looking for support. \"That's when I found out who really was my friend, and who wasn't, \"she said. \"Quite a few people stopped visiting me and asked their children not to play with Simona any more. Because of this, quarrels began in my family with each trouble brought about by her diagnosis. My husband became more and more unfriendly toward me and toward Simona. He didn't understand how important it was for Simona to receive regular examinations by a doctor or why she needed proper treatment for her sickness.\" When her mother tried to enroll Simona in a school, the teacher warned her that when other parents fo...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true according to this passage?", "options": ["Simona has been suffering from HIV for five years.", "Few people visited Simona's mother because of Simona's illness.", "Simona's mother received help from a social worker.", "Simona was accepted immediately by the first school."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1719, "question": "Computer technology is still developing rapidly. The computer of the future will continue to increase in value and performance while decreasing in cost. It will become smaller, but faster and more powerful. It is possible to make some guesses about what the future of the computer will look like, based upon the types of technologies that are being developed now. A lot of progress has already been made in some of these new technologies, but some are still in their earliest stages and may not be ready for use for years. Two of the most interesting areas of computing that are currently being developed are quantum computing and nanotechnology . Quantum computing is one possibility for the future of the computer that could make computers run far faster than even the quickest computers do today. ...\n\nQ: According to the text, quantum computing   _  .", "options": ["has been put in use so far", "can make computers run by themselves", "can reduce the cost of computers", "will work by using transistors"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2037, "question": "When on vacation,what do you look for in a hotel?Maybe you want a comfortable bed, or a suitable place.However,if you want something out of the ordinary and wish to go beyond the mundane, these spectacular hotels offer a stay you won't soon forget! Hippo Point For those who prefer an overnight stay with some four-footed or two-winged guests, Hippo offers unique rooms on the East African plains .The nine-story tower is treated as one of the top 10 resorts in the world.Guests enjoy incredible views of Olodian Bay.More than 520 species of birds gather around the lake,their calls sounding in the air. Dog Bark Park Inn At the Dog Bark Park Inn,sleeping in a doghouse is a good thing! Located near Cottonwood,Idaho,this bed and breakfast is inside the world's largest dog. Guests relax on dog-theme...\n\nQ: What does the phrase \"go beyond the mundane\" may mean?", "options": ["Do something exciting", "Go to a familiar place", "Look for a comfortable", "Travel in an ordinary way"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3456, "question": "\"Who does the cooking in your home?\" I'm often asked by my colleagues. \"My wife and I share it 50/50,\" I usually say without hesitation. It's a lie, of course. We're pretty much even when it comes to the children and the elderly. But the paying of bills isn't 50/50-my wife pays all sorts of household expenses, so I never even have to set eyes on them. And the cooking isn't 50/50, either. The truth is that I am the cook. On my recent 40th birthday, I received the following gifts from my children: a new pot, two mini bottles of truffle oil, a decorative salad-dressing pourer, and a juice-making machine. For a moment I longed for something more manly, a cricket bat, perhaps, and then had to admit that all these things would be useful for me. It's not that my wife can't or doesn't like to cook...\n\nQ: What do we know about the writer's wife?", "options": ["She can't cook.", "She doesn't like cooking.", "She used to cook for the family.", "She only knows how to make Welsh cakes."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 454, "question": "Does your local town have a nickname ? If so, what does it say about the area and the people who live there? Many cities are recognized across the world by their unofficial names. New York is the Big Apple, London is the Big Smoke, and Los Angeles is famously called La La Land. A project has been carried out to make a survey on how the nicknames of some places came about. The University of Winchester's Professor Bill Lucas is a patron of the English Project. He explains that unofficial place names often show what people think about a place. \"The name that people create for a place forms a connection with feelings,\" he says. Basingstoke is a town in central England. The local nickname, Amazingstoke, shows the love that locals seem to have for the area. Swindon, on the other hand, is sometim...\n\nQ: The best title of the passage can be   _  .", "options": ["People's Attitudes to Nicknames", "A Survey on Nicknames", "the Development of Nicknames", "the Usefulness of Nicknames"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1909, "question": "The ancient whistled language of the small island of La Gomera, off the coast of Africa, is about to disappear because of new technology and globalization. Now, a web company has taken on the task of saving the language by marrying history with technology. Silbo Gomero, a language used only on La Gomera Island, sounds to the untrained ear like few other known languages. The sounds that make up this language are made by whistling, rather than by speaking. The language was brought to the island by African setters many centuries ago. To communicate among the _ populated inland hills and valleys, shepherds had to use the whistled language, which could be heard and understood over distances of up to eight kilometers, compared to about 200 meters for a spoken word. With the development of new te...\n\nQ: In order to protect Silbo Gomero, Busuu.com   _", "options": ["teaches it on the Internet", "attracts people to visit La Gomero Island", "raises money to support students from La Gomero Island", "translates stories about it into other languages."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3324, "question": "Phyllis Lee of prefix = st1 /Singaporeknew something wasn't right. Her younger son, Alex, then six years old, was getting good grades in his private kindergarten classes. But Lee realized something was wrong when Alex came home one day, crying, with \"zeroes\" on his Chinese spelling test. Lee decided to investigate. According to Lee, the teacher would frequently describe Alex's Chinese writing as 'ghost writings' and made him a laughing stock in class instead of helping him out. Lee, 46, spent the next 12 months teaching Alex and still helps him when necessary. She not only taught him the formation of the Chinese words but also their origin so that he could understand better, often taking more than an hour to read a simple paragraph. Visits to the library and surfing the Internet kept her u...\n\nQ: For Alex the great achievement recently is that_.", "options": ["he gets A's in some subjects", "he wrote a book", "he earns some money", "he understands Chinese better"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2638, "question": "In Britain arrangements for inviting and entertaining guests at a wedding are usually the responsibility of the bride's family.In most cases it is mainly friends and relations of both families who are invited but when bride's father is a businessman of some kind, the wedding reception may provide a useful occasion for establishing social connections with clients or customers and other people whose goodwill may be of advantage to him.it is, however, the bride's mother who has the job of sending out the formal printed invitation cards. In the case of a church wedding, the vicar of each parish in which the bride and bridegroom live is normally informed about a month in advance of the ceremony so that an announcement of the coming wedding can be made in church on each of three Sundays before i...\n\nQ: It is the bride's parents who normally have to  _  .", "options": ["make all the arrangements for the wedding", "provide hospitality for the people attending", "decide who shall be invited", "pay all expenses involved"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 194, "question": "Chances are that you've had to apologize plenty of times in your life. And there's a goodchance that you've also expressed the phrase, \"I never meant to hurt you.\" Stop doing that, says author Caroline Myss. In a talk Myss - a spiritual researcher - took on the topic of forgiveness and healing, and explained in no uncertain terms why \"I never meant to hurt you\" is never a sufficient apology, no matter who it comes from. \"Picture that person coming up to you and saying, 'Wow, l'm sorry I did this, but, you know ,l never meant to hurt you. And, hey, can we just call it a day?\"' Myss says. Though it can make the two bur\\ the hatchet and keep friendship, that type of apology won't sit well with the person on the receiving end. \"That whole little thing - 'I never meant to hurt you' - that's the...\n\nQ: What is the author's purpose of writing the passage?", "options": ["To encourage people to apologize first.", "To tell people how to apologize sincerely.", "To introduce the topic of forgiveness and healing.", "To explain why people can't say \"I never meant to hurt you\"."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2531, "question": "As computers become more popular in China , Chinese people are increasingly relying on computer keyboards to input Chinese characters . But if they use the computer too much , they may end up forgetting the exact strokes of each Chinese character when writing on paper . Experts suggest people , especially students , write by hand more . Do you write by hand more or type more ? In Beijing , students start using a computer as early as primary school . And computer dependence is more widespread among university students . Almost all their assignments and essays are typed on a computer . All the students interviewed say they usually use a computer . It's faster and easier to correct if using a computer . And that's why computers are being applied more and more often to modern education . But w...\n\nQ: Which of the following can best serve as the title of the passage ?", "options": ["The Importance of Handwriting and Typing .", "To Type or to Handwrite .", "Writing by Computer Will Replace Writing by Hand", "Practical and Aesthetic Value of Chinese Characters"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1258, "question": "Yang Qunhui, 28, a graduate of Chengdu University of Information Technology, Sichuan Province, gave up her job with a monthly salary of 20,000 yuan ($3,014) at a famous company, but has started her own restroom-ad business with five other graduates, becoming a \"restroom queen.\" The company, opened in May, is now the only one of its kind in Chengdu. It has two goals: to find suitable restrooms to place ads and to find clients who are willing to put their ads in them. \"We are now trying to find restrooms to place the ads. A larger area means more ad sources,\" said Yang. Yang got the idea to run the company one year ago when she looked for toilet repairing information on the Internet but finally noticed companies in Beijing and Shanghai doing restroom ads. \"It's so interesting,\" she said. \"Ev...\n\nQ: The author's attitude towards restroom ads is   _  .", "options": ["positive", "negative", "doubtful", "not clear"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3068, "question": "There are one billion homeless people living in our world today . The Homeless World Cup exists to end this , so we all have a home , a basic human need . The Homeless World Cup is an annual , international football tournament , uniting teams of people who are homeless to take a once in a lifetime opportunity to represent their country and change their lives forever . It has inspired and supported over 50 grass roots football projects around the world working with homeless people throughout the year . The first tournament took place in Graz 2003 uniting 17 national teams . At the 5th Homeless World Cup in Copenhagen in 2004 , 48 nations , 500 players were united for a once in a lifetime opportunity to represent their country . 25,000 players were involved in pre-tournament training and tri...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true about the Copenhagen Homeless World Cup ?", "options": ["It took place in early December .", "25,000 players entered the tournament .", "Nearly 50 teams competed in the tournament .", "David Duke won the best goal scorer in 2004 ."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3144, "question": "My heroes are the Singapore Women's Everest Team.In 2009,they became the first all-women team to climb Mount Everest.The team of six young women trained for seven years before they climbed the mountain.It was difficult for them to train because Singapore doesn't have any snow or any mountains.But they didn't stop,and in the end they made it.They Worked hard every day for their dream so I really admire them. ----Lance Reed, 16, from Britain My mum,Mary Evans,is a real hero.I have a very big family, with two brothers and three sisters.My mum works very hard every day to look after us, and she is very busy.She always makes time for everyone and she always listens to me if I have a problem.I really respect my mum because she always looks after my family and makes sure we have everything we nee...\n\nQ: William admires the Salwen family's  _  .", "options": ["wealth", "courage", "success", "kindness"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2038, "question": "When on vacation,what do you look for in a hotel?Maybe you want a comfortable bed, or a suitable place.However,if you want something out of the ordinary and wish to go beyond the mundane, these spectacular hotels offer a stay you won't soon forget! Hippo Point For those who prefer an overnight stay with some four-footed or two-winged guests, Hippo offers unique rooms on the East African plains .The nine-story tower is treated as one of the top 10 resorts in the world.Guests enjoy incredible views of Olodian Bay.More than 520 species of birds gather around the lake,their calls sounding in the air. Dog Bark Park Inn At the Dog Bark Park Inn,sleeping in a doghouse is a good thing! Located near Cottonwood,Idaho,this bed and breakfast is inside the world's largest dog. Guests relax on dog-theme...\n\nQ: According to the passage,Hippo Point is intended for   _  .", "options": ["the sports fans", "the beach goers", "the bird lovers", "the dog owners"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 518, "question": "It's killed at least two dozen people, damaged hundreds of homes, cost some 22 billion Yuan in direct economic losses so far and has left thousands of family-bound travelers stranded. The massive snow and ice storm that has swept through the southern part of China has put this country into full disaster management mode. Tens of thousands of soldiers have been activated and the government has already provided 126 million Yuan in aide to six provinces in the south slammed by the unexpected winter blast. But is enough being done? And what else can be done to ensure that the effects of natural disasters like the one in southern China are minimized in the future? \"Ni hao, you're listening to People In the Know, your window into the world around you, online at www.crienglish.com here on China Ra...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of this article?", "options": ["Tell the stories about the snow storm in the southern part of China", "Tell us some facts about the people in the disaster.", "What have been done or will be done to rescue the people in the disaster.", "Let's know the measures about the disaster."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2716, "question": "The Sunset Pasta Cruise to Emerald Bay Saturday evening, September 25, 2010 You will cruise to Emerald Bay at Sunset, one of the most beautiful places in the world while dining on a Pasta Buffet and listening to live light dance music. Buses will pick up Sunset Pasta Cruise diners from the main entrance to the Horizon Casino Resort at: 4:40pm and 5:05pm on Saturday and take you the 1.5 miles to Ski Run Marina for boarding. Boarding is at Ski Run Marina at 5:15 p.m. (with departure at 5:45 p.m.), located in South Lake Tahoe. The cost for the cruise, pasta buffet, live music, and the 2.5-hour cruise to Emerald Bay is $55 (normally $75). The cost for children between 3-11 is $41 and under 3 is free. Must register the under 3 as well for the coast guard count. The Sunset Pasta Cruise will be l...\n\nQ: It can be inferred that Riva Grill is   _  .", "options": ["a supermarket", "a water sports center", "a restaurant", "a mall"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 847, "question": "Even if you are a good high-jumper, you can jump only about seven feet off the ground. You cannot jump any higher because the earth pulls you hard. The pull of the earth is called gravity. You can easily find out the pull of the earth. If you weigh yourself, you will know how much gravity is pulling you. Since there is gravity, water runs down hill. When you throw a ball into the air, it falls back down. Because of gravity, you do not fall off the earth as it whirls around. Then, can we get away from the earth and go far out into space? Now you can do it, because spaceships have been invented. Then spaceship will go so fast that it can escape the earth's gravity and carry you into space....\n\nQ: In this passage, the word \"gravity\" means  _  .", "options": ["the pull of everything.", "the force of attraction among objects.", "the force which attracts objects towards the centre of the earth", "the force which attracts the earth towards the sun."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2590, "question": "For years, experts have been encouraging people to exercise, using steps as simple as taking the stairs instead of a lift and walking to work, where possible. A recent study _ this advice -- it shows that frequent active exercise throughout the day can have great health benefits. The study, published in the magazinePreventive Medicine, found that just 2 minutes of stair-climbing several times a day can lower total cholesterol , raise HDL (\"good\") cholesterol and improve the heartbeat in young women who do not have much activity during the day.\"such improvements may have important effects on the health of women, since, like cigarette smoking, poor fitness have been shown to be a high risk for heart disease and death in women,\"said Dr.Colin Boreham with the University of Ulster in Belfast, I...\n\nQ: According to the study done by Dr.Boreham and his group, improvements in cholesterol levels are important in   _  .", "options": ["helping women to give up smoking", "enabling women to take exercise", "preventing women from having heart disease", "helping women to lose weight"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2033, "question": "Many adults in the United States can remember crying the nursery rhyme in the street \"Hot cross buns!\" But only a few people realize this was an early form of advertising. Written advertisements probably began with hieroglyphics more than three thousand years ago, but only a few people could read these symbols. So merchants made signs with pictures or hung their tools over their doors to identify their businesses. In the time of the Roman Empire, wall paintings were a popular form of advertisement. An ad for a play, or some other performance was painted on part of a building or on a wall around a city. People often advertised a house for rent or a freshwater bath in this way, too. Today, large wall signs are still used for outdoor advertising. But outdoor advertising is only a small fracti...\n\nQ: Which is the passage mainly discussing?", "options": ["Modern advertising", "Significance of advertising", "Development of advertising", "Origin of advertising"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2582, "question": "During a state of deep relaxation, several physiological changes take place in the body: the body's oxygen consumption is reduced; the heart beat decreases; muscle tension and sweating ease, and there is decreased sympathetic nervous system activity.This restful state not only allows the body to repair and restore itself, but it has a calming effect on the consciousness. How to achieve this state of relaxation, however, is a matter of opinion, and in some medical circles, a matter of controversy.A recent report by Dr.David Holmes of the University of Kansas in the journal \"American psychologist\" said that simply sitting in an armchair has just as many beneficial characteristics for the body as meditation does.Researchers of other relaxation techniques disagree.These experts believe that mo...\n\nQ: People seem to agree that   _  .", "options": ["sitting in an armchair benefits a person as meditation does", "structured relaxation techniques are more beneficial for a person", "to achieve a state of deep relaxation is possible through various means", "what people are all struggling for is a state of deep relaxation"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 968, "question": "The skin which covers the tips of the fingers and thumbs is crossed by numerous ridges arranged in different patterns. These patterns are permanent from birth and remain exactly the same throughout a person's life, even when the skin becomes wrinkled and cracked as a result of old age. Such patterns are never passed on from parents to children, and no one in the world has the same patterns as anyone else. Even identical twins have different sets of fingerprints. As a result, fingerprints offer a most useful and _ way of identifying people. Any ridged part of the hand and the foot may be used as a means of identification, but finger impressions are usually preferred since they can be taken easily and quickly. Fingerprints are classified in the ways: by general shapes and contours , by the f...\n\nQ: About the classification of fingerprints, which is TRUE?   _  .", "options": ["Fingerprints can be classified in three ways", "All fingerprints can be divided into 1, 024 groups and can not be divided further", "It is not easy to find a particular set of fingerprints in a short time", "People can not classify the fingerprints in an effective way"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2703, "question": "Hubert Joseph Schlafly was an electrical engineer who helped change the way actors, politicians and other people speak on television. In 1950, he and two other men developed the teleprompter. One co-worker, Fred Barton, was an actor. He had an idea for a tool that would help television actors read their lines without having to memorize them. The other co-worker was Irving Kahn. He worked as vice-president of radio and television at 20thCentury Fox. The first teleprompter involved a person who held a long piece of paper printed with big letters. As the actor read the lines, another person would move the paper ahead on the device . The teleprompter was first used on a television program called \"The First Hundred Years.\" Later versions used television screens to show the words that were to be...\n\nQ: What was the effect of the incident happening during Hoover's speech?", "options": ["The teleprompter became popular.", "Schlafly's invention was doubted.", "Schlafly set up his own company.", "Hoover didn't complete his speech."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 867, "question": "Most people who live in Seattle, Washington, love their city. There is a never-ending flow of fun things to do. But, people who live there do not always enjoy the day-after-day absence of sunshine during the winter months. It is documented fact that sunshine (or lack of it) plays a major role in how each of us meets the day. It also affects how we perform at school or work. When people are derived of sunlight, they can develop seasonal affective disorder, which makes it difficult for them to feel happy or get things accomplished. No major city in the United States is more affected by the \"sunshine factor\" than Seattle. To fight drizzle and fog during the winter months, Steve Murphy created a business that is very popular among the locals. The Indoor Sun Shoppe is more than a little ray of ...\n\nQ: Which of the following best explains the use of a dawn simulator?", "options": ["An alarm clock stimulated by the light rays of early morning.", "A bringer of indoor artificial sunshine when there is none outside.", "An automatic waterfall system helping make indoor plants healthy.", "A better way to meet a Seattle morning with real warming sunshine."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1380, "question": "One day a father and his rich family took his son on a trip to the country with the firm purpose to show him how poor people can be. They spent a day and a night on the farm of a very poor family. When they got back from their trip, the father asked his son, \"How was the trip?\" \"Very good, Dad!\" \"Did you see how poor people can be?\" the father asked. \"Yeah!\" \"And what did you learn?\" The son answered, \"I saw that we have a dog at home, and they have four. We have a pool that reaches to the middle of the garden; they have a creek that has no end. We have imported lamps in the garden; they have the stars. Our patio reaches to the front yard; they have a whole horizon.\" When the little boy finished, his father was speechless. The son added, \"Thanks, Dad, for showing me how poor we are!\" Isn't...\n\nQ: The son saw the following things EXCEPT_.", "options": ["a creek", "a lamp", "some stars", "a horizon"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1871, "question": "I recall a moment that I experienced with my dad when I was twenty-one. I was going to college and living with a couple of friends in Chicago. When the car I was using died, my dad, realizing that I needed transportation to get to work and to school, was good enough to lend me the money for a used car. Shortly after I bought it, my parents drove down to San Diego for the winter. Before they left, my dad gave me some of his bank deposit slips with clear and detailed instructions to put one hundred dollars of my earnings, every payday, into their savings account while they were gone. At that time of my life, I was not yet clear about what were the most important problems that I had to attend to first. I dismissed our agreement as nothing important and continued to spend my money as fast as I...\n\nQ: The writer mentions his own marriage and children at the end of the story in order to show   _  .", "options": ["his love for his own children", "his father's long-lasting influence", "his own happy family life", "his memory of his father"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 383, "question": "To err is human. To blame the other guy is even more human. Common sense is not all that common. Why tell the truth when you can come up with a good excuse? These three popular misquotes are meant to be jokes, and yet they tell us a lot about human nature .To err, or to make mistakes, is indeed a part of being human, but it seems that most people don't want to accept the responsibility for the problem. Perhaps it is the natural thing to do .The original quote about human nature went like this: \" To err is human, to forgive, divine .\"This saying mirrors an ideal people should be forgiving of others' mistakes. Instead, we tend to do the opposite -find someone else to pass the blame on to. However, taking responsibility for something that went wrong is a making of great maturity. Common sense...\n\nQ: Which of the following is N0T based on common sense?", "options": ["A man tries to take charge of everything in a large company.", "A student goes out with an umbrella in stormy weather.", "A company's next move follows a good plan.", "A lawyer acts on fine judgments."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1519, "question": "Women had a significant part to play during World War II,which was the time when women also made their own contributions.Some women's great efforts and their names have been recorded in history.Here's a look at some of the strong figures of women in World War II. Tatiana Nikolaevna Baramzina was born in Glazov of Russia on December 12,1919.In 1943,she was sent to the Central Women's Sniper Training School and upon her graduation in April,she was further sent to the front.She managed to kill around 16 enemies in the first three months!Unfortunately,she was captured by the enemies and was killed on the fifth of July in 1944.Today,the street where she grew up has been renamed in her memory. Anne Frank was a Germanborn Jewish girl who was wellknown for the publication of her diary that describ...\n\nQ: It can be learned from the text that   _  .", "options": ["Tatiana Baramzina was once a flight instructor", "Margaret Ringenberg was the best at writing about the war experiences", "Anne Frank and her family were arrested by Germans in 1944", "Hannah Szenes was arrested by Germans because of her diary"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 881, "question": "If you're in charge of a project, the key to success is getting everyone to want to help you. As a director, I point, I suggest, I gently push the actors in the direction I want them to go. In the 1986 movie Nothing in Common, Jackie Gleason's character, Max Basner, gets fired (or unemployed) from his job as a clothing salesman. The scene, shot on a boat, shows Max's despair about being out of work. I was looking for some gesture that would allow Max to show his feelings. Jackie had far more experience at everything than I did, and at first I was frightened (very much afraid). What could I possibly tell \"The Great One\" about acting? Out of fear I decided to direct by suggestion, and I sat down with Gleason to talk about the scene. \"So Max is sad, right?\" I said. Gleason nodded. \"And he's p...\n\nQ: It can be inferred   that   _  .", "options": ["Jackie Gleason is the director of the film Nothing in common", "Jackie Gleason is very angry when he is fired from his job", "Max, a character in a film, is in very low spirits when he loses his job", "Jackie Gleason is the writer of the film Nothing in common"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 0, "question": "The rain had continued for a week and the flood had created a big river which were running by Nancy Brown's farm. As she tried to gather her cows to a higher ground, she slipped and hit her head on a fallen tree trunk. The fall made her unconscious for a moment or two. When she came to, Lizzie, one of her oldest and favorite cows, was licking her face. At that time, the water level on the farm was still rising. Nancy gathered all her strength to get up and began walking slowly with Lizzie. The rain had become much heavier, and the water in the field was now waist high. Nancy's pace got slower and slower because she felt a great pain in her head. Finally, all she could do was to throw her arm around Lizzie's neck and try to hang on. About 20 minutes later, Lizzie managed to pull herself and...\n\nQ: What did Nancy try to do before she fell over?", "options": ["Measure the depth of the river", "Look for a fallen tree trunk", "Protect her cows from being drowned", "Run away from the flooded farm"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3091, "question": "How's your relationship with your dad? It can be easy to let walls build up between you during the teen years. But by taking several simple steps, you can help improve the relationship between the two of you--even without great efforts. Here are a few quick tips. Talk it out. Communication is key to any friendship. Open your mouth and let your dad know what's on your mind. Give him a chance to get to know you. Listen up. Your dad's lived more life than you have. Believe it or not, he's probably been there and can help you get through the pressures and struggles. Ask how he dealt with school, girls or temptations . Then pay attention. Take some time. It can be hard for us kids to talk about what really matters. But spending time together can build the relationship, and create chances to tal...\n\nQ: According to the writer,   _  .", "options": ["fathers have the right to guide teenagers", "respect means never fighting with fathers", "disagreements can be avoided through efforts", "always keeping your mouth closed really matters"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1915, "question": "Jack Benny was one of the most famous names in show business.He was born in Chicago,Illinois,on February 14th,1894.His parents,Meyer and Emma Kubelsky,were religious Jews.They had moved to the United States from Eastern Europe.Benny was a quiet boy.For much of the time,his parents were busy working in his father's store.As a child,Benny learned to play the violin.After finishing his school,he joined the Navy.He continued using his violin to perform for sailors.In one show he was chosen more for his funny jokes than for his skill with the violin.That experience made him believe that his future job was a comedian. Benny developed a show personality that had all the qualities people dislike.He was known for being so _ --he refused to spend any money unless forced to do so.On his shows Benny o...\n\nQ: Benny was determined to be a comedian after he   _  .", "options": ["left high school", "joined the Navy", "performed in a show for the sailors", "left the Navy for Broadway"], "answer": 2}]